[Music]
[Applause]
so
hello hello welcome to mikasa
before i show you the house let's check
out the ride
this here i think it's a 2003
toyota tacoma lots of dents you know
um i've actually driven this thing for
like 10 straight years
and uh i know it's probably worth like
five grand
at this point but i love it i just love
when i
when i have glute squad members ride in
the back with me
this part's really uncomfortable so i
put this pillow but everyone always gets
pissed who have to
let's just sit in the middle there but i
think it's funny i will not
upgrade i just don't care about cars
sometimes i think i should buy like some
fancy car but i just don't
care anyway on to the house
all right as you can see it's got a very
modern look
what i'm most proud of here is all the
decorations
if you look i got a lot of stuff hung up
on the walls
now i moved in here in
probably like october 7th or something
like that
and i had three weeks to throw a party
for my glute squad we had a halloween
party and i wanted it to look nice so i
did all this decorating in like three
weeks
[Music]
now some of this stuff i had at my last
house
but a lot of it i purchased off of
amazon target walmart
you'd be amazed at the stuff you can get
there
so first i want to highlight this couch
this is the legendary
love sack couch you can fit a lot of
people in here
you will often see my client jade
sleeping right here through
throughout the whole super bowl she will
be sound asleep
despite everything else going on um
but i do like these love sack couches
because you you can make them
huge it feels like you're it feels like
you're watching a movie you know
this tv it's the sony bravia
i don't know much about technology but
it is the best tv on the market
and what i really like is this tv stand
you know i can get this
like 180 degree turn if i wanted
and i could get it to pop out so much so
it kind of looks like you're
feels like you're in a movie theater a
little bit
[Music]
now all these plants in here are fake i
just don't know how to take care of
things i'm not good at it
i do not have a green thumb everything i
buy dies
so the fake plants look great though
check this out
that was uh painted a french artist
created this for me
based on a magazine cover that i was in
which i'll show you a bit later
here you got skelly
resting position now a lot of this stuff
has some meaning to me this here is a
calendar of my trip the glute squad made
this for me
a trip to cancun that we had um
here you got more of the same things
like this masa got for me my client masa
when i went to hawaii
my client elizabeth made this for me
see glute loops that's a picture of me
bret the serial killer see cereal get it
whenever i go to the zoo in san diego i
love watching the silverback gorillas
i've always loved silverbacks
i love king kong this is a
like eight inch sized brett contreras i
got this at one of the casinos in vegas
last year actually i think it was cosmo
i got this from the hawaii trip this
from the cancun trip
this is 300 you know uh leonidas
some of you followed me back in the
phoenix garage days and you know that i
had the movie 300 going on non-stop
there
that's one of my favorite movies right
here we got iron man
and iron man is actually like an
inspiration behind i'm not comparing
myself
to iron man but i wish like my dream is
to have this lab
where i can like create prototypes of
equipment and just have
like do it right there on the spot and
be like okay let's tweak this let's
tweak this and then
maybe one day i'll make it happen we
have a second
couch
and this actually gets used all the time
people have to sleep here when i have
parties
all right what's on the coffee table we
got glute lab
i always wanted this to have this nice
design where you'd be proud
to to showcase it on your coffee table
discover magazine i love my science this
is actually
this here is an iron man magazine from
july 1976 that's the month that i was
born it's really cool
to flip through here and see how all the
different equipment was
and to just see the differences in
equipment kind of cool how we've
come a long way but i love looking at
this stuff
and of course glute loops
i actually use these all the time while
i'm watching netflix
all right now on to the kitchen um
i'm going to tampa tomorrow on a trip so
i don't have much but i always have tons
of nuts
and seeds and dried fruit
big fan of dried fruit dried cherries
dried cranberries
peanut butter honey don't have much in
my
fridge you're gonna be disappointed but
i always have tons of yogurts greek
yogurts eggs
uh here is a shake that i was gonna make
in front of you guys
milk whey protein powder lots of honey
roasted peanuts in there and oats
throw it in here turn it on
[Music]
and it's ready to go i just open it up
ready to drink whoops all right one
thing
interesting about this house it was
built for really tall people i'm six
foot four
but this house is huge all these people
are like why are the countertops so high
and especially this microwave
why is it up so high people are five
feet tall can't even reach here they
have to have me get this stuff out
but yeah the previous owner of this
house was six foot four just like me
and his wife i think was like 5 10 she
was tall as well so they wanted a tall
person's house
all right in the pantry got lots of
stuff
got all my energy drinks here i just
only allow myself to have one a day
usually
uh funny i don't really drink alcohol
but it's loaded with
liquor these are for my parties but i
got all types of liquor and my glue
squad just wants tequila like this is
all they want is
right here they want patron they want
custom amigos
but i'm not a big drinker anymore i used
to we used to party a ton in my 20s
also i love my hot tamales i love
cinnamon
you might know me as the glute guy but
i'm also the cinnamon kid
seven rules of life don't you forget it
uh blender toaster air fryer
two different coffee makers and a
water boiler these are all for my goo
squad i don't drink tea or coffee
but they sure do here i got my calendar
you will be amazed i can have a calendar
i can have a things to-do list i can
write things down i will still forget
everything
i got my ring light here so that when i
do podcasts
i can face just have extra light coming
through the ring light
so here's where i normally do my
podcasts and things like that
always have a detailed things to do list
reminding me what i need to get done for
the day
this controls the jacuzzi
and here we have the famous bean bag
this is also
from lovesack
[Music]
now let me show you some of the bedrooms
alright
first this is the wooden room
for obvious reasons this cool wood this
like
pops out at you i really love the way
this looks but
this is actually my favorite painting in
the house makes me feel like i'm at the
beach
some of the so my glue squad this is
their favorite room they all have their
favorite rooms
the next room is the blue room
that's because all the things in here
are blue blue
blue
bathroom number one it's nice because
it's got that rainfall shower
[Music]
now this is the laundry room this is a
huge laundry room it's nice because
we have to do a lot of laundry here as
you can see uh
but yeah lots of laundry going on in
here
now we have the red room
obvious for obvious reasons there's
everything's red in here
uh this is actually the preferred room
for most people because
it has a bathroom
[Music]
so this is bathroom number two
i'm very proud of this thing right here
because i found a curved rod like you
get at the hotels
it's kind of surprisingly hard for me to
put together
this is the lost and found so many
people leave their stuff here
all the beds here you can incline the
head like this
and they're surprisingly comfortable
this is the famous mirror here lots of
selfies being taken in this mirror
so you'll see lots of selfies here
showing off their glutes
the i do think because it's slanted this
way it makes your lower body appear
bigger
so the girls that tend to be a little
bit slimmer they love the mirror because
it
makes their butts look bigger but the
girls who are a little bit
thicker they don't like it because it
makes them look even thicker
anyway overall this is a very popular
mirror
now on to my room
all right welcome to my room this bed
right here now
this is where the magic happens
big time and
and when i say magic maybe not the magic
you're thinking of
more like this
being single these days it's a little
disappointing it's a badass bed and
here's why
if i hit this button
it vibrates and it's pretty powerful the
whole bed vibrates
i'm addicted to this it rocks me to
sleep
but i can also as you can see the that
that is inclined on the both the foot
and the head
and i can choose to incline or decline
the foot here i'll
drop the foot down see that
now i'll drop the head down but i
actually like having them both inclined
something interesting about me i am the
worst sleeper
it's a double-edged sword it's why i'm
so productive but i also
am tired throughout life a lot of times
i sleep this way
[Music]
that's always annoyed my girlfriends
because in the middle of night i'll wake
them up i'm like can we sleep this way
but i will read
so my head will be here and i'll read
like here so i'll have a little reading
light
like that okay and i'll put it right
here and i'll just read until i can't
you know tell me about to fall asleep
then i turn the light off
but i have this little step thing so i
can just put the book right on there
also if you press this button back here
there's an
led light underneath the bed and you can
make it different colors like
blue green red purple
i don't use that very often but it's
cool okay now since i'm such a poor
sleeper i don't like sound
sound wakes me up so i use this guy
[Music]
so it's a fan sound and you can choose
different fan noises and
white noises but this is my favorite
some people love it it drives other
people crazy some people like i don't
know how you sleep like that
all right here's the tulum uh
here's a picture of the tulum trip
and then i got like lots of new york and
then this tiger i like because blue is
my favorite color
now i want to show you some of my
accolades
this is my first personal trainer
certification from american council on
exercise or ace
here is my emt certification uh
this is from like 2000. arizona teacher
and substitute teacher certification
these are from way back in the day right
this is my master's degree this is from
asu
this is my high school diploma shadow
mountain high school this is in
phoenix arizona nau that's my bachelor's
degree
from flagstaff
all right now some of the stuff more
specific to
strength and conditioning cscs with
distinction there okay
with distinction proud of that i love
the nsca now here are some of my
trademarks and patents so this is my
patent
on the hip thruster okay very proud of
this
um got that in 2012 but i actually
applied for it in 2009.
here's trademark on glute loop trademark
on booty by brett
this is my the magazine i told you about
earlier
i was on the cover of scottsdale health
look at that
beard majestic beard right there
that was right that was like a week
before my 40th birthday
that was before the gray set in okay
now this is my phd diploma right
and this is my
dissertation right here this was from
2016.
see this is on basically squats versus
hip thrusts
horizontal versus vertical exercises
see kinematics kinetics and
electromyography of vertical and
horizontal hip extension exercises and
their transference to acceleration and
power
this is from aut
in new zealand
here we go body weight strength training
anatomy and all the different languages
that it was translated into and this is
glute lab
and now glute labs translate into
different languages as well
and this is strong curves so these are
the three books i've written
here's some of the magazines that i've
been on
uh been inside these different magazines
like
there's a there's an article i did
i actually showed this in my last
youtube video here's a
drawing that i made them do but yeah
this is
an article on glutes that i was heavily
involved in
um but yeah all of these
[Music]
it's in this one too and that there's me
at glute lab doing smith machine hip
dress
same thing
really cool
here men's health gives advice from the
top 20
gyms in the us and
interestingly glute lab phoenix arizona
was
number five
it was really an honor to be featured as
one of the top 20 gyms
this is men's health inside the ass
factory
my buddy andre but please crack me up
right here
he made me extra jacked right here's me
doing goblet squats
sideline hip abductions extra range
so yeah and then here's some of my
published papers well this was my first
article that ever got popular this was
dispelling the glute myth this was my
first
published study to crunch or not to
crunch
that was 2011 and this is my
first published original research this
was from 2015
a comparison of gluteus maximus biceps
femoris and vastus lateralis
electromyographic activity and the back
squat and barbell hip dust exercises
this sketchbook is from 2006
this is 15 years old and this was when i
first thought up the hip thrust
and here's some of these old original
drawings
right this is kind of like a plate
loaded booty builder right here
see that i even got him like
notarized in case someone came up with
an invention
after i did it i hadn't patented it yet
well yeah this was
october 25th of 2006.
this was the idea for the very first hip
thruster this thing sucked
but yeah
i called it the scorcher and these
different drawings here
now let's address the elephant in the
room
a tanning bed
just open her up hit start boom
[Music]
i know what you're thinking who the hell
has a tanning bed in their own room but
sometimes i'm busy i don't have time to
lay out so i like to do this a few times
a week and stay tan
okay this is my closet
this is a no judgment zone i'm not the
neatest guy
but lots of jorts in here
tons of jorts tons of tank tops right
these guys here
most of my clothes i get from amazon
i'm just not the nicest dresser in the
world i don't care about that either
my client sarah got this for me this
bidet and it's a game changer
i i don't like i don't like going the
bathroom without a bidet anymore why
doesn't every toilet have a bidet
now we got the bathtub with this
rainforest like background
i have not used this yet but i do fit in
it uh
i didn't think i could fit because i
never fit inside of bathtubs but i
actually
tried this and i would fit i've just
never taken baths before so
i don't know i guess i could usually you
have to have your whole torso out when
you're tall like me
or your whole legs out but here i could
actually
use it if i wanted to relax i just
i don't i need to get over the hump and
try it
and now one of the coolest things about
my house
this here is a steam room okay
so we got steam
and i can sit at whatever temperature i
want
[Music]
i use this almost every single night
love it now i'm wet
[__] now let me show you the upstairs
game room
[Music]
all right we got the marker board to try
and keep me organized
with all my social media stuff
this is actually where my camera guy
alex lives
here i got on this couch but the couch
turns into a bed how do you turn it
pull this out
oh wow so this is alex's bed
but then also a couch and this here is
his computer station it's pretty badass
so we added all the youtube videos here
we got two glute lab cantina signs
[Music]
i designed this with my niece gabby it's
pretty cool because
uh we we designed that together
it took us like 20 minutes but
she liked this one a lot more she liked
those colors
with the orange and the green and the
the light blue and the pink but i like
these colors better
with the red the blue the yellow and the
green
we couldn't decide so i got two of them
i think it's funny because glute lab san
diego doesn't even have an official sign
it just has a banner
and glute lab cantina has two different
neon signs
all right now some cool game stuff here
is a ping pong table
here's a large connect four
uh i am unbeaten in connect four i'm
warning you
i'm pretty good at this if you're as
good as me
then it comes down to whoever gets to go
first wins
here we got an arcade game you can play
pac-man and stuff like that there's a
bunch of different games from the 80s on
here
pool table
[Music]
here we got corn hole here we have a
dartboard
[Music]
here we've got a bartending station
all right so if we have parties up here
we get the music going
it's a lot of fun but yeah we can
actually have a bartender serving drinks
and here's a little fridge
and then finally here
oh my god
here is where we film the youtube videos
so
you might recognize this background this
is where the youtube videos are filmed
with this background
now you might be wondering right now
why is this here i have not
had i have not figured out how to use it
yet
but in one of my youtube videos i would
just want to tell a really bad joke
and then nobody laughs and then this
tumbleweed just
flies across the room so prepare for
that one day it will be used
and there we have alex's bathroom
[Music]
i had to install this shower for him
kind of close call here with how close
the toilet is but
but he ain't complaining
[Music]
all right here's the balcony i need to
get furniture for the balcony but
here we got the pool and the jacuzzi you
can see it's a nice
green lawn there's always rabbits and
road runners and
tons of different type of wildlife out
here it's pretty cool
there's also some good mountain scenery
on both sides unfortunately my
neighbor's yards aren't the best things
to look at but
if you can ignore that
[Music]
now this was supposed to be here
and this is supposed to be here
[Music]
and these are supposed to be here
but the problem is somebody forgot to do
it
somebody forgot to hang these up whose
fault was that
i wonder whose fault that is
alex thank you for fessing up
now i also bought this adjacent property
so one day i want to build on that um
i haven't figured out what yet but i
will build something badass
on that property so that that's the
adjacent lot i own as well
now let me show you the backyard
[Music]
this is the pool this is the jacuzzi
what i love about this place is so quiet
and peaceful
[Music]
the most peaceful place i've ever lived
during the day there's no noise
i know this has a name but i can't think
of it but it's only a few inches deep
this is going to come in handy during
the summer
[Music]
this is the glute squad's favorite zone
they love to lay out this is the famous
influencer wall i got tons of my squad
that took pictures
i would never look at that and think
there would be a good place for pictures
but
i don't have an eye like they do
you know how bad i would have killed for
a backyard like this growing up i mean
we could have played
with football and football and all sorts
of sports volleyball
yeah we could have had a field day here
you can see these glute lab lights up
there and i have neon lights in my
garage too sometimes i wonder what it
looks like from people who drive by
all right now let me show you the gym
[Music]
all right this is glute lab las vegas
this is a four car
1200 square foot garage gym actually
think it's 1300 but
um you know i put rubber flooring down i
put mirrors
i put little neon lights around it i
boxed in like the water heater and
things like that
that are things that are unsightly but
let me show off some of my equipment
here's where we do squats bench chin ups
and military press
i love these little guys that i got off
amazon except this
it fall backwards clearly whoever made
this doesn't even lift
where we do high step ups i drag this
out we do high step ups
nordics
this is my nordic ham curl machine very
proud of this this is my hammy track and
roller
this free motion cable column is so
smooth i'm so glad i got it it's
expensive
you know i thought about getting a used
one but i'm really glad i bought the
brand new
free motion because it's so smooth it
just everything feels amazingly
comfortable off of it
now this is glute lab but it also could
be called delt lab here i've got a
lateral raised machine
i can actually do this stack the stack
and these two extra weights
for 12 reps right now so i've gotten
really strong at this thing
[Music]
here's my adduction machine
you might not know this about me but i
have really
muscular adductors my legs are pretty
scrawny but my adductors are super
strong
i can do the stack plus these extra
weights for 55 reps
i've never met anyone who has stronger
adductors than me and then
the seated hip abduction machine so this
never gets used by
any of my glute squad members only by me
but this gets used all the time
the ladies love it i can also do the
whole stack for 55 reps on these so
i have good abduction adduction strength
here's where we do back extensions
we got a smith machine
this is for leg extensions and seated
leg curls
there are dumbbells
here i've got a plate loaded shoulder
press machine
and i actually prefer using it uh
facing this way and one arm at a time
masta's boyfriend chris turned me on to
that and i think it's better that way
here's where we do our glute bridges
here is a nautilus glute drive
this is a speaker we use this for our
parties and we use it here in the gym
but
it's really amazing it gets so loud then
the base is amazing
here we got the t-bell
and the blocks so this is where we do
our stradalis and finally
this is where the thrusting occurs
this is my hip thruster the favorite of
all my inventions
so it's a very bc strength oriented gym
what's cool is this parking lot goes
forever
so theoretically it could be like
lunge all the way up and back i wonder
how many steps that would be that would
probably be
200 steps for me 300 for one of my
shorter clients but yeah
so you can do stuff out here as well
here's a here's a better view of the
mountains from the side here
and then here eventually we're going to
get blinds
so we don't have to have aluminum foil
on the windows but that's just a
blockout light so we can film youtube
videos during the day
i've showed you where i eat i showed you
where i sleep i showed you where i lived
i showed you where i bathe
i even showed you where i make love to a
woman so i can't think of anything else
to show you
now it's time for you to get the [__]
out
all right this was a unique video i
don't do stuff like this often so in the
comments section let me know if you like
seeing this type of stuff
or if you'd prefer just strictly
strength training
strictly thrusting strictly hip breath
strictly glutes
welcome to mikasa i hope you enjoyed the
video
[Music]
you